http://www.appa.com.au/privacy-policy

Cart
Member Login
Search
AboutAbout UsAPPA Code of ConductBoard of DirectorsOur CommitteesAPPA StaffCharity PartnerGovernance and StrategyDigital Advertising RatesPromotional ProductsWhat is a Promotional Product?Product Search (Public Access)Product Search (Member Access)Promotional Product SafetyPromotional Products WorkBuyer Beware StatementMembersBecome a MemberFind an APPA MemberMember BenefitsService ProvidersPromotional Products Marketing MagazineIndustry BenchmarkingLegal Resources PlatformLife MembersTestimonialsResourcesAPPA Logo GuidelinesDigital Product CataloguesEvents & EducationAPPA AwardsAPPA Awards 2020Past APPA Awards WinnersTradeshowsWebinarsLive Product DemonstrationsFactory ToursAPPA Product Safety Training ProgramCertificationTalking Promo Podcast SeriesAPPA SearchNews
CareersPromotional Products WorkTradeshowsFAQContact Us
Connect
×
Login Or Join
User Login
E-mail: * Password: *
Create new account
Request new password
Privacy Policy
General
APPA gathers two types of information about users of this website:
Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions including registering for APPA’s trade shows.Information APPA gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout APPA’s websites.
This information allows APPA to better tailor the content of this website and to track the demographics of APPA’s audience. APPA reserves the right to share information amongst its membership base.
Usage Tracking
APPA tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of APPA’s websites. However, APPA does not correlate this information with data about individual users. APPA breaks down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).
APPA may on occasion track and catalogue the search terms that users enter in the Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. APPA uses tracking information to determine which areas of APPA’s websites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas.
APPA does not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps APPA continue to build a better service for you.
Cookies
APPA may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself should not contain personal information although it will enable APPA to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information which you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. APPA uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). APPA’s advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys.
Sharing of Information
APPA uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help APPA better understand APPA’s audience's demographics. This is essential to keeping APPA’s service free. APPA will share personal information about individual users to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of APPA’s users or the public.
APPA will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by APPA and for other compatible purposes.APPA will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.APPA will ensure that personal information collected should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.APPA will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.APPA will make readily available to customers information about APPA’s policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.Without limiting paragraph (a) above, APPA may disclose your personal information to its advisers and such other parties as necessary to fulfil APPA’s purposes or if APPA is required to make such disclosure by law.
Security
APPA operates secure data network protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. APPA’s security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by APPA’s customers.
When paying for your APPA trade show booking online, your financial details are passed through a secure server using 128-bit SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption technology.
If you have any questions regarding APPA’s security policy, please contact APPA at info@appa.com.au
Your Consent
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by APPA. If APPA decides to change APPA’s privacy policy, APPA will post those changes on this website so that you are always aware of what information APPA collects, how it is used, and under what circumstances it may be disclosed.
APPA’s privacy policy is applicable to all persons who use this website (which includes viewing, using or otherwise interacting with this website) and, for the avoidance of doubt, is not limited to users who are members and service providers of APPA.
APPASuite 7, 407 Canterbury Road, Surrey Hills VIC, 31271800 MY APPAwww.appa.com.auinfo@appa.com.au
+61 1800 692 772
Contact Us
Quick Links
About APPA Member Benefits Career Centre Join APPA APPA Tradeshows
© 2020 Australasian Promotional Products Association (APPA)
Privacy PolicyTerms and Conditions
